ekowarehouse.com 2015-09-16

# Ekowarehouse Privacy Policy - Global Wholesale Organic & Green Products For Exporters, Traders, Importers, Distributors, Manufacturers, Retailers, Brands | Ekowarehouse

This privacy policy sets out how Ekowarehouse Limited uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.

Ekowarehouse Limited is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Ekowarehouse Limited may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1 November 2013.

We require your information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emailsabout new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. 
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Ekowarehouse Limited will not share, lease or sell your personal and/or company data with any organizations, individuals or third parties, unless required to do so by Hong Kong S.A.R. law. Ekowarehouse Ltd will not benefit from or use your personal and/or company data in any other way other than to conduct its stated services.

Ekowarehouse Ltd cannot be held responsible for the loss or misuse of any personal and/or company data, which is accessed by unauthorized persons due to circumstances beyond our reasonable control.

By using this site, you agree to opt-in to our site’s use of cookies. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Ekowarehouse Ltd is fully compliant with the Hong Kong S.A.R. Data Protection Ordinance.

You can contact us at anytime at [privacy@ekowarehouse.com](mailto:privacy@ekowarehouse.com) should you wish to discuss our privacy policy or know more about how we make use of your personal and/or company data.
